# **NAVEEN KHAN**

# (FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER)

OAddress :- Gwalior Kampoo Lashkar MP 474001

naveenkhan9516@gmail.com

+91-9171739795

#### **SUMMARY**

I experienced front-end developer with good skills and knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, and Vue.js and so have two years of work experience. I master creating dynamic, stylish web applications that use the base UI/UX principles effectively. Innovation and teamwork are my driving force.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Front-End web developer(Internships), EIBO SERVICES PVT LTD

Jan 2021 - Jan 2022

- A specific project during the internship involve developing a new feature for the company's website, such as an interactive product configurator
- Utilizing modern frameworks and libraries such as React.js.
- Creating HTML, css, and javascript-based visual and responsive designs. by the focuses on designing the structure, navigation, and other features.

Web Developer Jan 2022 - Dec 2023

- Worked together with the marketing team to create 10+ advertisement projects for local and global clients
- Worked individually to conceptualize the website design for new changes on the company's website and successfully chosen

# Data Science (ML/DL), Data Analysis (Internship)

May 2023 - Jan 2024

- Coordinated project tasks, ensuring Research Paper and Data Science Using Python and Machine Learning Techniques
- Conducted comprehensive project analyses, identifying and rectifying discrepancies in Deep Learning and Machine Learning and using Pandas, Numpy, OpenCV, Scikit learn ETC.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor of Technology in CSE**

Aug 2018 - Aug 2023

Gwalior Institute of Information Technology (GIIT)

Relevant coursework in Structural Design and Technology of Computer Science Engineering

# **Higher Secondary School (12th)**

Jul 2017 - Apr 2018

Board Of Secondary Education, Madhya Pradesh, Bhopal

- Specialization in Science.
- Math, Physics, Chemistry and Biology Passed with First Division

# **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

- Technical Skills: Data Analysis, Responsive web design, HTML5, Bootstrap, React.Js
- Languages: English, Spanish, Hindi
- Certifications: Data Tableau Data analysis certificate by Jobaaj Learning, Front-end developing certificate by EIBO Services Pvt Ltd.
- Awards/Activities: Received the NCC Certificate for Being an NCC cadet by 15 MP BN (MP18SDA221635)